Against the Sun is a war, adventure film directed by Brian Falk.
A WWII pilot, bombardier, and radioman find themselves adrift on a lifeboat without food or
water after being forced to ditch their plane during a scouting mission.
Tony Pastula, played by Tom Felton.
Harold Dixon, played by Garret Dillahunt.
Gene Aldrich, played by Jake Abel.
Frances, played by Nadia Parra.
Against the Sun is a 2014 American survival drama film.
Based on a true story from World War II, the film was written, produced, and directed
by Brian Falk and starred Garret Dillahunt, Tom Felton, and Jake Abel.
The film was released via video on demand on January 23, 2015.
The film explores themes of world war ii, survival, lifeboat, bombardier.